It's not a disease.
It's a curse.
They complained of frequent nosebleeds
and auditory hallucinations.
It suddenly begins one day
and it never stops.
They turned into miserable,
desperate beings.
Throw it!
Humans will not be able to overcome this.
Help us!
-I was consumed by it too.
-Protect them?
Is that what you want?
You're fine.
Probably thanks to the golden hour.
There was someone who knew about this
before the government announcement.
If subjects hold out for 15 days
without being consumed
they enter a stable period.
They become half-monsters,
dangerous and volatile beings.
We called them special infectees.
Hyun-su is dangerous.
He's dangerous, but we need him.
You're just being used.
You think I'll hurt you guys
if I become a monster?
A monster is a monster.
Humans have failed.
Accept it.
Surrender the infected immediately.
Survivors will be transferred
to a shelter.
This "shelter" sounds ridiculous.
You don't know
who'll turn into a monster when.
There's a good chance it's a lie.
I'll come back.
No. Eun-hyeok!
You promised to come back!
Eun-hyeok!
Your fiancé.
I know where he is
and what happened to him.
Humans and we can't coexist anyway.
I'm going to find more that are like us.
SPECIAL INFECTEE REPORT GUIDE
Come with me.
Cha Hyun-su.
Long time no see.
BAMSEOM EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT BUREAU
CENTRAL COMMAND
Any improvements in his condition?
Doesn't seem that way.
Then he has no value to us.
So why is he still alive?
Because he's still breathing.
Not because he's your friend?
I'm the one who put him in this state.
Don't you remember?
Fair enough. Any new findings?
BAMSEOM EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT BUREAU
C5 RESEARCH FACILITY
I do have a theory.
Earth came into existence
4.6 billion years ago,
and we, the Homo Sapiens,
emerged 200,000 years ago.
Count that as a single day,
and we'll only have existed
for three seconds.
What are you trying to say?
Mankind is nothing
from Earth's perspective.
But these worthless beings
are getting on its nerves.
They're destroying everything
to fulfill their greed
and killing off other species.
At this point, Earth must be thinking,
"It's time to let another species
take the reins, humans.
You've been around long enough,
don't you think?"
So here's my theory.
Mankind is a virus.
And the monsters are the vaccine.
ORIGINAL STORY WEBTOON SWEET HOME
BY CARNBY KIM AND YOUNGCHAN HWANG
SWEET HOME
This is Central Command.
A vehicle transporting
a special infectee has been hijacked.
Pursuit team, report in.
The rest, support them.
BAMSEOM EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT BUREAU
RESTRICTED MILITARY AREA
Black Kite Three,
this is a crucial mission.
Return immediately.
The subject being escorted
is extremely dangerous.
Your safety will be ensured
if you surrender.
Pretty arrogant of you to say
you'll ensure my safety.
Who are you? What do you want?
I'm nobody.
And I don't want anything.
There's gotta be a reason
you're doing this, you bastard!
To give you a chance, I guess?
Who are you?
What the hell are you--
Cha Hyun-su.
Long time no see.
Jung Ui-myeong.
You recognized me right away?
That's no fun.
This is Black Kite Nine.
The vehicle carrying the special infectee
is headed toward Hannam.
Vehicle is approaching the Banpo Bridge.
Calling for backup.
Why did you kill Sang-wook?
Because of you.
I didn't like the look in your eyes.
Die!
Die--
This guy's still alive.
All thanks to me.
You should be thanking me.
So ungrateful, Hyun-su.
-The vehicle is ahead of us.
-Use all the firepower we've got.
Stop them at the bridge at all costs.
There seems to be action
inside the vehicle.
Pursuit team,
check on the special infectee first!
The special infectee is still alive!
Stop resisting it and unleash it.
You…
can't kill me.
This is Night Owl. Cutting them off.
Launching.
The vehicle is pressing forward!
Failed to stop the vehicle.
It's headed toward Banpo.
Requesting permission for direct fire.
Negative.
We have to capture the target alive.
He's the last living special infectee.
Shoot down the bridge
to block the escape route.
This is Night Owl One.
The vehicle is getting away.
Lost visual on the target.
Check the possible escape routes
and get on its tail!
Pursuit team, find another route
and search every place they could hide.
Aren't there enough monsters
captured at Central Command?
-Why are you being so reckless--
-Because they're special!
They're neither human nor monster!
We need them to make a cure. Got that?
Did they succeed?
The special infectees
at Central Command are useless now.
They'll probably be discarded.
That's why we have to
capture them at all costs.
The soldiers did it.
Does that mean we're safe now?
There wasn't a single monster
on our way here.
There weren't any people either.
Well, that's probably because…
the soldiers already rescued them all.
This is the Dumugae checkpoint.
A military vehicle carrying survivors
is approaching.
Inspecting the vehicle.
See? I told you.
We don't see anything unusual.
We're letting them through.
Roger.
How long until the debris is cleared?
About a couple of hours.
We'll start moving
the survivors in the back too.
No! He's just sick!
He has leukemia.
There must be a doctor at the shelter.
You can check with them!
Okay. We'll check.
Tae-yun will be okay.
No signs of recovery.
He's not a monster.
Good.
Get rid of him.
-What the hell did you just do?
-Back off.
-A nosebleed is a serious symptom.
-You sons of bitches!
No…
Die, motherfucker.
Die!
You piece of shit.
Baby.
My baby!
Don't do that!
No, Yeong-chan!
You can't do that.
Yeong-chan, my baby…
You're in high spirits.
Humming and whatnot.
What the hell are you saying?
That wasn't you?
What's this sound then?
Ready or not, here I come
I'm going to find you
Move!
You! Where do you think you're going?
I…
I heard something back there.
-Scan it.
-Nothing there, sir.
What the hell are you trying to pull?
Hey, shut up and get back to work.
Turn around!
Go on.
Go!
Move it!
Ready or not, here I come
I'm going to find you
Run.
Run!
Over here!
Get over here! Come on!
Hurry!
Come on!
Hurry up!
Let's go!
-Hurry!
-Hey!
Start driving!
You son of a bitch!
Let's go, asshole!
Hey! Start driving!
You asshole!
Mommy.
Mommy!
-Mommy!
-Don't shoot!
Let me go!
Mommy…
Yun-seo!
Oh, no!
Mommy!
Yun-seo!
Are you trying to get us
all fucking killed?
I thought the soldiers would be okay.
-You bastard.
-Bom…
You piece of shit.
Bom isn't here.
Who cares about your damn dog?
We barely survived.
You would've died if it weren't for Bom!
You ran away on your own back there.
You selfish bastard.
What's so wrong about that?
Stop it. This isn't the time to argue.
What's going to happen to us now?
Wait, what's in your hand?
You motherfucker.
You gotta be kidding me.
Do you even know how to use that?
What do you want?
There's somewhere I need to be.
They didn't retreat after seeing that?
Those reckless idiots.
SPECIAL INFECTEE REPORT GUIDE
Sergeants Kim Yeong-hu and Min Seo-jin.
Take your teams and search the area.
We'll back you up from here.
Search every corner.
Report to me if you find something.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Kim.
Something's wrong here.
Doesn't this seem familiar?
Most of them were shot to death.
Any traces of monsters?
I doubt a monster shot them.
The corpses would be in pieces
if they were attacked by monsters.
Judging by the mess,
they were here for sure.
Most of the bodies here
have gunshot wounds as well.
They might have already gotten away.
Stand back.
I'm detecting a monster
in the debris up ahead, sir.
Target location confirmed.
I think it's hiding in the debris.
Permission to blow it up, sir.
Granted.
There are more than one.
We got one here as well.
Cease fire!
It's headed your way, Kim.
Prepare to fire.
Seok-chan, you're with me!
The monster is moving
rapidly toward the front.
Where the fuck did that come from?
Hey!
Back off if you want to
save your offspring.
Back off!
Hold this, Seok-chan.
Mommy…
That's enough.
Out of the way.
What are you doing, sir?
You just let a monster live.
"Kill any monster on sight
to stop this crisis."
That's our mission
as the Crow Platoon, isn't it?
Sergeant First Class Kim.
We only take out monsters
that harm humans.
That's…
the Crow Platoon's mission.
We need to make a good first impression.
We're about to meet others like us.
"Special infectee"?
I fucking hate that name.
Any ideas?
How about "neohuman"?
Does it still hurt?
I didn't mean to do that.
Sorry.
So your plan is to go on a shopping spree?
Why did you bring me here?
So you could live.
I didn't want you to be captured
and regret it all.
I saved you so you can live in freedom.
Humans won't give up.
They captured and then lost you,
so they'll feel anxious
and chase you down until the end.
I don't care.
It was my decision.
That's right.
You handed yourself over to the soldiers.
Why?
I told you.
That they'll puncture you
and rip you apart over and over again.
I told you countless times!
Is that why you ran?
Because you were scared?
I just wanted to live.
Find a new purpose.
Don't think about saving mankind
and all that crap.
Think about how you want to live.
There's gotta be a reason
you became a neohuman.
I don't want to live like you
at the cost of others' lives.
Help me!
Mine!
Bring it here!
Help me!
Mine!
-Mine!
-Help me!
-Give me!
Help--
I don't want to fight you.
So from now on,
I won't kill anyone without a reason.
You mean that?
Absolutely!
I promise I won't harm anyone first.
Unless they get in the way.
Dior.
Hermès.
How will you find
more beings like us?
We don't have to.
We're going to them right now.
They're all locked up in Bamseom,
where they were taking you.
I was going there anyway.
So why did you…
No, that's not…
That's not it.
You would have looked pathetic.
We can't be dragged there.
We'll walk in there ourselves.
Aren't you excited?
You'll be saving neohumans this time.
You'll know when you meet them.
The reason you were chosen.
This is Gate 2.
Unreported Black Kite vehicle approaching.
Major.
Weren't you out on an operation?
We have an urgent report to make.
You have to sign the log
and have your identity confirmed.
Don't you know me?
I told you it was urgent. Open up!
The vehicle is clear. It's coming through.
BAMSEOM EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT BUREAU
How far do you think you can make it?
Do you think my soldiers will stand around
when their commander is gone?
We passed the gate with no problem.
That means no one's reported you missing.
The military is too busy
to be worried about you.
All troops. It's an emergency.
Two men presumed to be
special infectees are approaching.
All troops, return to the base immediately
and reinforce security at Gate 2.
I thought I forgot about it all.
But I still remember the pain
as clear as day.
We survived…
in this world.
We should live more decently
as human beings.
Get out.
Get out of my head!
Stay away.
Get away from me!
You monster.
Why are you doing this to us?
Just kill me.
I don't want to hurt anymore.
Mom…
Beginning the test on sample D-126.
Hui-ji.
The subject is
the biological mother of D-126.
She volunteered for the test.
-Her type?
-Yellow.
According to the mother,
she suffered from hate comments.
Where are you, Hui-ji? It's Mom.
Hui-ji.
Hui-ji, Mom's here.
Is that you?
Hui-ji, it's me.
Hui-ji.
Bonds formed pre-monsterization
had no effect on a Type Yellow.
Test over.
No!
No, Hui-ji!
No! Let go of me!
No!
Hui-ji!
Hui-ji…
No!
No, Hui-ji!
I shouldn't have taken this fucking body.
I definitely shouldn't have.
I never liked this son of a bitch.
Why the fuck isn't it working?
Running away again?
God damn it.
Did you say we were chosen?
You're wrong.
We were abandoned.
Look at you.
You can't live without humans.
You are…
nothing but a parasite.
Fuck you!
Shut up, you piece of shit.
Come with me.
Let go.
Let go, you motherfucker.
Let go!
Let go, you son of a bitch!
I'll fucking kill you!
Fucking son of a bitch.
Let go.
Let go, you motherfucker!
Son of a bitch. I'm going to kill you.
I'll fucking kill you, motherfucker!
I'll kill you.
Try to hang in there.
Two is better than one, don't you think?
Crazy bastard.
You think they'll accept you
as a human being?
Fuck.
You'll be ripped apart
for pointless experiments
and end up regretting everything!
Please.
I can't go back there.
We'll both die in there!
Please.
Please don't do this.
Look at me.
I can't go back there.
Please!
Please.
Why the hell
won't you believe me?
Why?
Because I don't want to forget.
I don't ever want to forget…
the fact…
that I'm human.
Fine.
Welcome to hell.
Subtitle translation by Jea-heon Chung
Modify by Blue-Bird™